<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://pfcstyle.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://pfcstyle.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-05-17T13:46:40+08:00</updated><id>https://pfcstyle.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">01手记</title><subtitle>Will的个人手记</subtitle><author><name>Yawei Wang</name></author><entry><title type="html">Piek 隐私政策</title><link href="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2023/03/30/piek-privacy-cn/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Piek 隐私政策" /><published>2023-03-30T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2023-03-30T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://pfcstyle.github.io/2023/03/30/piek-privacy-cn</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2023/03/30/piek-privacy-cn/"><![CDATA[<p>本应用尊重并保护所有使用服务用户的个人隐私权。为了给您提供更准确、更有个性化的服务，本应用会按照本隐私权政策的规定使用和披露您的个人信息。但本应用将以高度的勤勉、审慎义务对待这些信息。除本隐私权政策另有规定外，在未征得您事先许可的情况下，本应用不会将这些信息对外披露或向第三方提供。本应用会不时更新本隐私权政策。 您在同意本应用服务使用协议之时，即视为您已经同意本隐私权政策全部内容。本隐私权政策属于本应用服务使用协议不可分割的一部分。</p>

<h2 id="1-适用范围">1. 适用范围</h2>

<p>(a) 在您注册本应用帐号时，您根据本应用要求提供的个人注册信息；</p>

<p>(b) 在您使用本应用网络服务，或访问本应用平台网页时，本应用自动接收并记录的您的浏览器和计算机上的信息，包括但不限于您的IP地址、浏览器的类型、使用的语言、访问日期和时间、软硬件特征信息及您需求的网页记录等数据；</p>

<p>(c) 本应用通过合法途径从商业伙伴处取得的用户个人数据。</p>

<p>您了解并同意，以下信息不适用本隐私权政策：</p>

<p>(a) 您在使用本应用平台提供的搜索服务时输入的关键字信息；</p>

<p>(b) 本应用收集到的您在本应用发布的有关信息数据，包括但不限于参与活动、成交信息及评价详情；</p>

<p>(c) 违反法律规定或违反本应用规则行为及本应用已对您采取的措施。</p>

<h2 id="2-信息使用">2. 信息使用</h2>

<p>(a)本应用不会向任何无关第三方提供、出售、出租、分享或交易您的个人信息，除非事先得到您的许可，或该第三方和本应用（含本应用关联公司）单独或共同为您提供服务，且在该服务结束后，其将被禁止访问包括其以前能够访问的所有这些资料。</p>

<p>(b) 本应用亦不允许任何第三方以任何手段收集、编辑、出售或者无偿传播您的个人信息。任何本应用平台用户如从事上述活动，一经发现，本应用有权立即终止与该用户的服务协议。</p>

<p>(c) 为服务用户的目的，本应用可能通过使用您的个人信息，向您提供您感兴趣的信息，包括但不限于向您发出产品和服务信息，或者与本应用合作伙伴共享信息以便他们向您发送有关其产品和服务的信息（后者需要您的事先同意）。</p>

<h2 id="3-信息披露">3. 信息披露</h2>

<p>在如下情况下，本应用将依据您的个人意愿或法律的规定全部或部分的披露您的个人信息：</p>

<p>(a) 经您事先同意，向第三方披露；</p>

<p>(b)为提供您所要求的产品和服务，而必须和第三方分享您的个人信息；</p>

<p>(c) 根据法律的有关规定，或者行政或司法机构的要求，向第三方或者行政、司法机构披露；</p>

<p>(d) 如您出现违反中国有关法律、法规或者本应用服务协议或相关规则的情况，需要向第三方披露；</p>

<p>(e) 如您是适格的知识产权投诉人并已提起投诉，应被投诉人要求，向被投诉人披露，以便双方处理可能的权利纠纷；</p>

<p>(f) 在本应用平台上创建的某一交易中，如交易任何一方履行或部分履行了交易义务并提出信息披露请求的，本应用有权决定向该用户提供其交易对方的联络方式等必要信息，以促成交易的完成或纠纷的解决。</p>

<p>(g) 其它本应用根据法律、法规或者网站政策认为合适的披露。</p>

<h2 id="4-信息存储和交换">4. 信息存储和交换</h2>

<p>本应用收集的有关您的信息和资料将保存在本应用及（或）其关联公司的服务器上，这些信息和资料可能传送至您所在国家、地区或本应用收集信息和资料所在地的境外并在境外被访问、存储和展示。</p>

<h2 id="5-cookie的使用">5. Cookie的使用</h2>

<p>(a) 在您未拒绝接受cookies的情况下，本应用会在您的计算机上设定或取用cookies ，以便您能登录或使用依赖于cookies的本应用平台服务或功能。本应用使用cookies可为您提供更加周到的个性化服务，包括推广服务。</p>

<p>(b) 您有权选择接受或拒绝接受cookies。您可以通过修改浏览器设置的方式拒绝接受cookies。但如果您选择拒绝接受cookies，则您可能无法登录或使用依赖于cookies的本应用网络服务或功能。</p>

<p>(c) 通过本应用所设cookies所取得的有关信息，将适用本政策。</p>

<h2 id="6-信息安全">6. 信息安全</h2>

<p>(a) 本应用帐号均有安全保护功能，请妥善保管您的用户名及密码信息。本应用将通过对用户密码进行加密等安全措施确保您的信息不丢失，不被滥用和变造。尽管有前述安全措施，但同时也请您注意在信息网络上不存在“完善的安全措施”。</p>

<p>(b) 在使用本应用网络服务进行网上交易时，您不可避免的要向交易对方或潜在的交易对方披露自己的个人信息，如联络方式或者邮政地址。请您妥善保护自己的个人信息，仅在必要的情形下向他人提供。如您发现自己的个人信息泄密，尤其是本应用用户名及密码发生泄露，请您立即联络本应用客服，以便本应用采取相应措施。</p>

<h2 id="7-本隐私政策的更改">7. 本隐私政策的更改</h2>

<p>(a) 如果决定更改隐私政策，我们会在本政策中、本公司网站中以及我们认为适当的位置发布这些更改，以便您了解我们如何收集、使用您的个人信息，哪些人可以访问这些信息，以及在什么情况下我们会透露这些信息。</p>

<p>(b) 本公司保留随时修改本政策的权利，因此请经常查看。如对本政策作出重大更改，本公司会通过网站通知的形式告知。</p>

<p>方披露自己的个人信息，如联络方式或者邮政地址。请您妥善保护自己的个人信息，仅在必要的情形下向他人提供。如您发现自己的个人信息泄密，尤其是本应用用户名及密码发生泄露，请您立即联络本应用客服，以便本应用采取相应措施。</p>]]></content><author><name>Yawei</name></author><category term="privacy" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[本应用尊重并保护所有使用服务用户的个人隐私权。为了给您提供更准确、更有个性化的服务，本应用会按照本隐私权政策的规定使用和披露您的个人信息。但本应用将以高度的勤勉、审慎义务对待这些信息。除本隐私权政策另有规定外，在未征得您事先许可的情况下，本应用不会将这些信息对外披露或向第三方提供。本应用会不时更新本隐私权政策。 您在同意本应用服务使用协议之时，即视为您已经同意本隐私权政策全部内容。本隐私权政策属于本应用服务使用协议不可分割的一部分。]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Piek Privacy</title><link href="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2023/03/30/piek-privacy-en/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Piek Privacy" /><published>2023-03-30T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2023-03-30T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://pfcstyle.github.io/2023/03/30/piek-privacy-en</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2023/03/30/piek-privacy-en/"><![CDATA[<p>This application respects and protects the personal privacy of all service users. In order to provide you with more accurate and personalized services, this application will use and disclose your personal information in accordance with the provisions of this privacy policy. However, this application will treat this information with a high degree of diligence and prudence. Except as otherwise provided in this privacy policy, this application will not disclose or provide this information to third parties without your prior permission. This application will update this privacy policy from time to time. When you agree to this application service use agreement, you are deemed to have agreed to the entire content of this privacy policy. This privacy policy is an integral part of this application service usage agreement.</p>

<h2 id="1-scope-of-application">1. Scope of application</h2>

<p>(a) When you register for this application account, you provide personal registration information according to the requirements of this application;</p>

<p>(b) When you use this application network service or visit the application platform webpage, this application automatically receives and records the information on your browser and computer, including but not limited to your IP address, browser type, Data such as the language used, the date and time of the visit, the characteristics of software and hardware, and the webpage records you require;</p>

<p>(c) This application obtains user personal data from business partners through legal means.</p>

<p>You understand and agree that the following information does not apply to this privacy policy:</p>

<p>(a) The keyword information you enter when using the search service provided by this application platform;</p>

<p>(b) The relevant information and data that you publish in this app collected by this app, including but not limited to participation in activities, transaction information and evaluation details;</p>

<p>(c) Violation of legal provisions or violations of the rules of this application and the measures that this application has taken against you.</p>

<h2 id="2-use-of-information">2. Use of Information</h2>

<p>(a) This app will not provide, sell, rent, share or trade your personal information to any unrelated third party, unless you have obtained your permission in advance, or the third party and this app (including this app affiliate) individually or jointly To provide you with services, and after the end of the service, it will be prohibited from accessing all these materials that it was able to access before.</p>

<p>(b) This application also does not allow any third party to collect, edit, sell or disseminate your personal information by any means. If any user of this application platform engages in the above activities, once discovered, this application has the right to immediately terminate the service agreement with the user.</p>

<p>(c) For the purpose of serving users, this application may use your personal information to provide you with information that is of interest to you, including but not limited to sending you product and service information, or sharing information with partners of this application for them Send you information about its products and services (the latter requires your prior consent).</p>

<h2 id="3-information-disclosure">3. Information Disclosure</h2>

<p>Under the following circumstances, this application will disclose your personal information in whole or in part according to your personal wishes or legal requirements:</p>

<p>(a) Disclosure to a third party with your prior consent;</p>

<p>(b) In order to provide the products and services you request, you must share your personal information with third parties;</p>

<p>(c) Disclosure to a third party or administrative or judicial institution in accordance with relevant provisions of the law or the requirements of an administrative or judicial institution;</p>

<p>(d) If you violate relevant Chinese laws, regulations, or this application service agreement or related rules, you need to disclose to a third party;</p>

<p>(e) If you are a qualified intellectual property complainant and have filed a complaint, you should disclose it to the respondent at the request of the respondent, so that both parties can deal with possible rights disputes;</p>

<p>(f) In a transaction created on this application platform, if any party to the transaction fulfills or partially fulfills its transaction obligations and makes an information disclosure request, this application has the right to decide to provide the user with the contact information of the counterparty, etc. Information to facilitate the completion of the transaction or the resolution of disputes.</p>

<p>(g) Other disclosures deemed appropriate by this application in accordance with laws, regulations or website policies.</p>

<h2 id="4-information-storage-and-exchange">4. Information storage and exchange</h2>

<p>The information and data collected by this application about you will be stored on the servers of this application and/or its affiliated companies. This information and data may be sent to your country, region or outside the country where the application collects the information and data, and in Visited, stored and displayed outside the country.</p>

<h2 id="5-use-of-cookies">5. Use of Cookies</h2>

<p>(a) If you do not refuse to accept cookies, this application will set or access cookies on your computer so that you can log in or use the services or functions of this application platform that rely on cookies. This application uses cookies to provide you with more thoughtful and personalized services, including promotional services.</p>

<p>(b) You have the right to choose to accept or refuse to accept cookies. You can refuse to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. But if you choose to refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to log in or use the web services or functions of this application that rely on cookies.</p>

<p>(c) This policy will apply to the relevant information obtained through the cookies set in this application.</p>

<h2 id="6-information-security">6. Information Security</h2>

<p>(a) This application account has security protection function, please keep your user name and password information properly. This application will use security measures such as encrypting user passwords to ensure that your information is not lost, abused and altered. Despite the aforementioned security measures, please note that there is no “perfect security measure” on the information network.</p>

<p>(b) When using this application network service to conduct online transactions, you will inevitably disclose your personal information, such as contact information or postal address, to the counterparty or potential counterparty. Please properly protect your personal information and only provide it to others when necessary. If you find that your personal information is leaked, especially the user name and password of this application, please contact the customer service of this application immediately so that this application can take corresponding measures.</p>

<h2 id="7-changes-to-this-privacy-policy">7. Changes to this privacy policy</h2>

<p>(a) If you decide to change the privacy policy, we will post these changes in this policy, on our company’s website, and where we deem appropriate, so that you can understand how we collect and use your personal information and who can access this information. And under what circumstances we will disclose this information.</p>

<p>(b) The company reserves the right to modify this policy at any time, so please check it frequently. If you make a major change to this policy, the company will notify you through a website notice.</p>

<p>Parties disclose their personal information, such as contact information or postal address. Please properly protect your personal information and only provide it to others when necessary. If you find that your personal information is leaked, especially the user name and password of this application, please contact the customer service of this application immediately so that this application can take corresponding measures.</p>]]></content><author><name>Yawei</name></author><category term="privacy" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This application respects and protects the personal privacy of all service users. In order to provide you with more accurate and personalized services, this application will use and disclose your personal information in accordance with the provisions of this privacy policy. However, this application will treat this information with a high degree of diligence and prudence. Except as otherwise provided in this privacy policy, this application will not disclose or provide this information to third parties without your prior permission. This application will update this privacy policy from time to time. When you agree to this application service use agreement, you are deemed to have agreed to the entire content of this privacy policy. This privacy policy is an integral part of this application service usage agreement.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">ArcGIS Spark 隐私政策</title><link href="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/07/29/spark-privacy-cn/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ArcGIS Spark 隐私政策" /><published>2021-07-29T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2021-07-29T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/07/29/spark-privacy-cn</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/07/29/spark-privacy-cn/"><![CDATA[<p>本应用尊重并保护所有使用服务用户的个人隐私权。为了给您提供更准确、更有个性化的服务，本应用会按照本隐私权政策的规定使用和披露您的个人信息。但本应用将以高度的勤勉、审慎义务对待这些信息。除本隐私权政策另有规定外，在未征得您事先许可的情况下，本应用不会将这些信息对外披露或向第三方提供。本应用会不时更新本隐私权政策。 您在同意本应用服务使用协议之时，即视为您已经同意本隐私权政策全部内容。本隐私权政策属于本应用服务使用协议不可分割的一部分。</p>

<h2 id="1-适用范围">1. 适用范围</h2>

<p>(a) 在您注册本应用帐号时，您根据本应用要求提供的个人注册信息；</p>

<p>(b) 在您使用本应用网络服务，或访问本应用平台网页时，本应用自动接收并记录的您的浏览器和计算机上的信息，包括但不限于您的IP地址、浏览器的类型、使用的语言、访问日期和时间、软硬件特征信息及您需求的网页记录等数据；</p>

<p>(c) 本应用通过合法途径从商业伙伴处取得的用户个人数据。</p>

<p>您了解并同意，以下信息不适用本隐私权政策：</p>

<p>(a) 您在使用本应用平台提供的搜索服务时输入的关键字信息；</p>

<p>(b) 本应用收集到的您在本应用发布的有关信息数据，包括但不限于参与活动、成交信息及评价详情；</p>

<p>(c) 违反法律规定或违反本应用规则行为及本应用已对您采取的措施。</p>

<h2 id="2-信息使用">2. 信息使用</h2>

<p>(a)本应用不会向任何无关第三方提供、出售、出租、分享或交易您的个人信息，除非事先得到您的许可，或该第三方和本应用（含本应用关联公司）单独或共同为您提供服务，且在该服务结束后，其将被禁止访问包括其以前能够访问的所有这些资料。</p>

<p>(b) 本应用亦不允许任何第三方以任何手段收集、编辑、出售或者无偿传播您的个人信息。任何本应用平台用户如从事上述活动，一经发现，本应用有权立即终止与该用户的服务协议。</p>

<p>(c) 为服务用户的目的，本应用可能通过使用您的个人信息，向您提供您感兴趣的信息，包括但不限于向您发出产品和服务信息，或者与本应用合作伙伴共享信息以便他们向您发送有关其产品和服务的信息（后者需要您的事先同意）。</p>

<h2 id="3-信息披露">3. 信息披露</h2>

<p>在如下情况下，本应用将依据您的个人意愿或法律的规定全部或部分的披露您的个人信息：</p>

<p>(a) 经您事先同意，向第三方披露；</p>

<p>(b)为提供您所要求的产品和服务，而必须和第三方分享您的个人信息；</p>

<p>(c) 根据法律的有关规定，或者行政或司法机构的要求，向第三方或者行政、司法机构披露；</p>

<p>(d) 如您出现违反中国有关法律、法规或者本应用服务协议或相关规则的情况，需要向第三方披露；</p>

<p>(e) 如您是适格的知识产权投诉人并已提起投诉，应被投诉人要求，向被投诉人披露，以便双方处理可能的权利纠纷；</p>

<p>(f) 在本应用平台上创建的某一交易中，如交易任何一方履行或部分履行了交易义务并提出信息披露请求的，本应用有权决定向该用户提供其交易对方的联络方式等必要信息，以促成交易的完成或纠纷的解决。</p>

<p>(g) 其它本应用根据法律、法规或者网站政策认为合适的披露。</p>

<h2 id="4-信息存储和交换">4. 信息存储和交换</h2>

<p>本应用收集的有关您的信息和资料将保存在本应用及（或）其关联公司的服务器上，这些信息和资料可能传送至您所在国家、地区或本应用收集信息和资料所在地的境外并在境外被访问、存储和展示。</p>

<h2 id="5-cookie的使用">5. Cookie的使用</h2>

<p>(a) 在您未拒绝接受cookies的情况下，本应用会在您的计算机上设定或取用cookies ，以便您能登录或使用依赖于cookies的本应用平台服务或功能。本应用使用cookies可为您提供更加周到的个性化服务，包括推广服务。</p>

<p>(b) 您有权选择接受或拒绝接受cookies。您可以通过修改浏览器设置的方式拒绝接受cookies。但如果您选择拒绝接受cookies，则您可能无法登录或使用依赖于cookies的本应用网络服务或功能。</p>

<p>(c) 通过本应用所设cookies所取得的有关信息，将适用本政策。</p>

<h2 id="6-信息安全">6. 信息安全</h2>

<p>(a) 本应用帐号均有安全保护功能，请妥善保管您的用户名及密码信息。本应用将通过对用户密码进行加密等安全措施确保您的信息不丢失，不被滥用和变造。尽管有前述安全措施，但同时也请您注意在信息网络上不存在“完善的安全措施”。</p>

<p>(b) 在使用本应用网络服务进行网上交易时，您不可避免的要向交易对方或潜在的交易对方披露自己的个人信息，如联络方式或者邮政地址。请您妥善保护自己的个人信息，仅在必要的情形下向他人提供。如您发现自己的个人信息泄密，尤其是本应用用户名及密码发生泄露，请您立即联络本应用客服，以便本应用采取相应措施。</p>

<h2 id="7-本隐私政策的更改">7. 本隐私政策的更改</h2>

<p>(a) 如果决定更改隐私政策，我们会在本政策中、本公司网站中以及我们认为适当的位置发布这些更改，以便您了解我们如何收集、使用您的个人信息，哪些人可以访问这些信息，以及在什么情况下我们会透露这些信息。</p>

<p>(b) 本公司保留随时修改本政策的权利，因此请经常查看。如对本政策作出重大更改，本公司会通过网站通知的形式告知。</p>

<p>方披露自己的个人信息，如联络方式或者邮政地址。请您妥善保护自己的个人信息，仅在必要的情形下向他人提供。如您发现自己的个人信息泄密，尤其是本应用用户名及密码发生泄露，请您立即联络本应用客服，以便本应用采取相应措施。</p>]]></content><author><name>Yawei</name></author><category term="privacy" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[本应用尊重并保护所有使用服务用户的个人隐私权。为了给您提供更准确、更有个性化的服务，本应用会按照本隐私权政策的规定使用和披露您的个人信息。但本应用将以高度的勤勉、审慎义务对待这些信息。除本隐私权政策另有规定外，在未征得您事先许可的情况下，本应用不会将这些信息对外披露或向第三方提供。本应用会不时更新本隐私权政策。 您在同意本应用服务使用协议之时，即视为您已经同意本隐私权政策全部内容。本隐私权政策属于本应用服务使用协议不可分割的一部分。]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">ArcGIS Spark Privacy</title><link href="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/07/29/spark-privacy-en/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ArcGIS Spark Privacy" /><published>2021-07-29T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2021-07-29T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/07/29/spark-privacy-en</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/07/29/spark-privacy-en/"><![CDATA[<p>This application respects and protects the personal privacy of all service users. In order to provide you with more accurate and personalized services, this application will use and disclose your personal information in accordance with the provisions of this privacy policy. However, this application will treat this information with a high degree of diligence and prudence. Except as otherwise provided in this privacy policy, this application will not disclose or provide this information to third parties without your prior permission. This application will update this privacy policy from time to time. When you agree to this application service use agreement, you are deemed to have agreed to the entire content of this privacy policy. This privacy policy is an integral part of this application service usage agreement.</p>

<h2 id="1-scope-of-application">1. Scope of application</h2>

<p>(a) When you register for this application account, you provide personal registration information according to the requirements of this application;</p>

<p>(b) When you use this application network service or visit the application platform webpage, this application automatically receives and records the information on your browser and computer, including but not limited to your IP address, browser type, Data such as the language used, the date and time of the visit, the characteristics of software and hardware, and the webpage records you require;</p>

<p>(c) This application obtains user personal data from business partners through legal means.</p>

<p>You understand and agree that the following information does not apply to this privacy policy:</p>

<p>(a) The keyword information you enter when using the search service provided by this application platform;</p>

<p>(b) The relevant information and data that you publish in this app collected by this app, including but not limited to participation in activities, transaction information and evaluation details;</p>

<p>(c) Violation of legal provisions or violations of the rules of this application and the measures that this application has taken against you.</p>

<h2 id="2-use-of-information">2. Use of Information</h2>

<p>(a) This app will not provide, sell, rent, share or trade your personal information to any unrelated third party, unless you have obtained your permission in advance, or the third party and this app (including this app affiliate) individually or jointly To provide you with services, and after the end of the service, it will be prohibited from accessing all these materials that it was able to access before.</p>

<p>(b) This application also does not allow any third party to collect, edit, sell or disseminate your personal information by any means. If any user of this application platform engages in the above activities, once discovered, this application has the right to immediately terminate the service agreement with the user.</p>

<p>(c) For the purpose of serving users, this application may use your personal information to provide you with information that is of interest to you, including but not limited to sending you product and service information, or sharing information with partners of this application for them Send you information about its products and services (the latter requires your prior consent).</p>

<h2 id="3-information-disclosure">3. Information Disclosure</h2>

<p>Under the following circumstances, this application will disclose your personal information in whole or in part according to your personal wishes or legal requirements:</p>

<p>(a) Disclosure to a third party with your prior consent;</p>

<p>(b) In order to provide the products and services you request, you must share your personal information with third parties;</p>

<p>(c) Disclosure to a third party or administrative or judicial institution in accordance with relevant provisions of the law or the requirements of an administrative or judicial institution;</p>

<p>(d) If you violate relevant Chinese laws, regulations, or this application service agreement or related rules, you need to disclose to a third party;</p>

<p>(e) If you are a qualified intellectual property complainant and have filed a complaint, you should disclose it to the respondent at the request of the respondent, so that both parties can deal with possible rights disputes;</p>

<p>(f) In a transaction created on this application platform, if any party to the transaction fulfills or partially fulfills its transaction obligations and makes an information disclosure request, this application has the right to decide to provide the user with the contact information of the counterparty, etc. Information to facilitate the completion of the transaction or the resolution of disputes.</p>

<p>(g) Other disclosures deemed appropriate by this application in accordance with laws, regulations or website policies.</p>

<h2 id="4-information-storage-and-exchange">4. Information storage and exchange</h2>

<p>The information and data collected by this application about you will be stored on the servers of this application and/or its affiliated companies. This information and data may be sent to your country, region or outside the country where the application collects the information and data, and in Visited, stored and displayed outside the country.</p>

<h2 id="5-use-of-cookies">5. Use of Cookies</h2>

<p>(a) If you do not refuse to accept cookies, this application will set or access cookies on your computer so that you can log in or use the services or functions of this application platform that rely on cookies. This application uses cookies to provide you with more thoughtful and personalized services, including promotional services.</p>

<p>(b) You have the right to choose to accept or refuse to accept cookies. You can refuse to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. But if you choose to refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to log in or use the web services or functions of this application that rely on cookies.</p>

<p>(c) This policy will apply to the relevant information obtained through the cookies set in this application.</p>

<h2 id="6-information-security">6. Information Security</h2>

<p>(a) This application account has security protection function, please keep your user name and password information properly. This application will use security measures such as encrypting user passwords to ensure that your information is not lost, abused and altered. Despite the aforementioned security measures, please note that there is no “perfect security measure” on the information network.</p>

<p>(b) When using this application network service to conduct online transactions, you will inevitably disclose your personal information, such as contact information or postal address, to the counterparty or potential counterparty. Please properly protect your personal information and only provide it to others when necessary. If you find that your personal information is leaked, especially the user name and password of this application, please contact the customer service of this application immediately so that this application can take corresponding measures.</p>

<h2 id="7-changes-to-this-privacy-policy">7. Changes to this privacy policy</h2>

<p>(a) If you decide to change the privacy policy, we will post these changes in this policy, on our company’s website, and where we deem appropriate, so that you can understand how we collect and use your personal information and who can access this information. And under what circumstances we will disclose this information.</p>

<p>(b) The company reserves the right to modify this policy at any time, so please check it frequently. If you make a major change to this policy, the company will notify you through a website notice.</p>

<p>Parties disclose their personal information, such as contact information or postal address. Please properly protect your personal information and only provide it to others when necessary. If you find that your personal information is leaked, especially the user name and password of this application, please contact the customer service of this application immediately so that this application can take corresponding measures.</p>]]></content><author><name>Yawei</name></author><category term="privacy" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This application respects and protects the personal privacy of all service users. In order to provide you with more accurate and personalized services, this application will use and disclose your personal information in accordance with the provisions of this privacy policy. However, this application will treat this information with a high degree of diligence and prudence. Except as otherwise provided in this privacy policy, this application will not disclose or provide this information to third parties without your prior permission. This application will update this privacy policy from time to time. When you agree to this application service use agreement, you are deemed to have agreed to the entire content of this privacy policy. This privacy policy is an integral part of this application service usage agreement.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Android Reverse - The APK exported from AndroidKiller can’t be installed</title><link href="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/06/23/android-reverse-android-killer-apk-install/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Android Reverse - The APK exported from AndroidKiller can’t be installed" /><published>2021-06-23T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2021-06-23T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/06/23/android-reverse-android-killer-apk-install</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/06/23/android-reverse-android-killer-apk-install/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="问题">问题</h1>

<p>使用AndroidKiller编译签名的apk无法安装，报错：</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>Targeting R+ (version 30 and above) requires the resources.arsc of installed APKs to be stored uncompressed and aligned on a 4-byte boundary</p>
</blockquote>

<p>这是因为没有4k对齐导致的问题，可以通过使用zipalign工具手动对齐</p>

<p>zipalign工具目录：G:\AndroidSDK\build-tools\30.0.2, 基本各个版本的Android都有，选一个即可</p>

<div class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>zipalign -f -p 4 input.apk output.apk
</code></pre></div></div>

<p>注意，需要先对齐，再签名。因为新版现在都要求使用v2及以上的签名版本，新版本是对所有包内内容进行的hash,对齐会导致hash变化从而导致签名验证失败。</p>

<p>签名命令：</p>
<div class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code># apksigner与zipalign在同一目录
 apksigner sign --ks welltory.jks  --ks-pass pass:123456 --v2-signing-enabled true output.apk
</code></pre></div></div>]]></content><author><name>Yawei</name></author><category term="Android" /><category term="Reverse" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Targeting R+ (version 30 and above) requires the resources.arsc of installed APKs to be stored uncompressed and aligned on a 4-byte boundary]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Xcode: unsupported OS version for new iOS</title><link href="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/06/10/xcode-unsupported-os-version/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Xcode: unsupported OS version for new iOS" /><published>2021-06-10T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2021-06-10T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/06/10/xcode-unsupported-os-version</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/06/10/xcode-unsupported-os-version/"><![CDATA[<p>You can download device support file from <a href="https://github.com/iGhibli/iOS-DeviceSupport/tree/master/DeviceSupport">GitHub</a>, then add it in path <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">/Applications/Xcode.app/contents/Developer/platform/iPhoneOS.platform/DeviceSupport</code></p>]]></content><author><name>Yawei</name></author><category term="Xcode" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can download device support file from GitHub, then add it in path /Applications/Xcode.app/contents/Developer/platform/iPhoneOS.platform/DeviceSupport]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Describe your hometown</title><link href="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/06/06/describe-your-home/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Describe your hometown" /><published>2021-06-06T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2021-06-06T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/06/06/describe-your-home</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/06/06/describe-your-home/"><![CDATA[<p>scenic spot</p>

<p>flat area</p>

<p>I’d prefer to go to a place with amusement parks, shopping centers and</p>

<p>I’d or I would look for a place with natural landscape</p>

<p>You can go sightseeing</p>

<p>it has four distinctive seasons</p>]]></content><author><name>Yawei</name></author><category term="English" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[scenic spot]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Who does chores</title><link href="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/05/30/who-does-chores/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Who does chores" /><published>2021-05-30T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2021-05-30T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/05/30/who-does-chores</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/05/30/who-does-chores/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="some-sentences">Some sentences</h1>

<p>In my home both my husband and myself do the chores.</p>

<p>I hire people to the painting.</p>

<p>She had the windows washed yesterday. // This means she hired someone to wash the window</p>

<p>I washed the windows yesterday. // This means I washed the window myself.</p>]]></content><author><name>Yawei</name></author><category term="English" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some sentences]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Describe a challenge</title><link href="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/05/29/describe-a-scary-story/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Describe a challenge" /><published>2021-05-29T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2021-05-29T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/05/29/describe-a-scary-story</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/05/29/describe-a-scary-story/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="elements-of-a-scary-story">Elements of a scary story</h1>

<ul>
  <li>weird atmosphere</li>
  <li>unknown factors</li>
  <li>scary feeling</li>
  <li>scary characters: zombies, ghosts</li>
  <li>horrible music / people</li>
  <li>darkness</li>
  <li>haunted houses</li>
  <li>abandoned houses</li>
  <li>Bloody</li>
  <li>Terrible animal</li>
</ul>

<h1 id="some-horrific-sounds">Some horrific sounds</h1>

<ul>
  <li>Creak: make a harsh, high-pitched sound when being moved or when pressure or weight is applied.</li>
  <li>Rattle: make or cause to make a rapid succession of short, sharp knocking sounds</li>
  <li>Cackle: a horrible, scary laugh</li>
  <li>Wind is howling: the sound that the wind makes.</li>
  <li>Echo: the sound a bat makes</li>
</ul>

<h1 id="grammar">Grammar</h1>

<ul>
  <li><del>I just go/ return to my home and call my mum with crying.</del> I just went / returned to my home and call my mum crying.</li>
  <li><del>I have experienced.</del> I experienced / I had experienced.</li>
  <li><del>I don’t have many experiences of scary.</del> I don’t have many scary experiences.</li>
  <li><del>A snake come up.</del> A snake came up.</li>
  <li><del>Any scared experiences.</del> Any scary experiences.</li>
  <li><del>There were 2 person.</del> There were 2 people.</li>
  <li>I remember very clearly.</li>
  <li><del>I was happen.</del> It happened.</li>
  <li><del>It is very scared.</del> It is very scary.</li>
  <li>Whisper in someone’s ear.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Yawei</name></author><category term="English" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elements of a scary story]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Describe a challenge</title><link href="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/05/27/describe-a-challenge/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Describe a challenge" /><published>2021-05-27T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2021-05-27T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/05/27/describe-a-challenge</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pfcstyle.github.io/2021/05/27/describe-a-challenge/"><![CDATA[<p>The hardest thing I’ve ever had to do…</p>
<h1 id="key-words-and-phrases">key words and phrases</h1>
<ul>
  <li>In spite of …</li>
  <li>Regardless of …</li>
  <li>
    <p>Despite …</p>
  </li>
  <li>determined</li>
  <li>resolute</li>
  <li>steadfast</li>
  <li>unshakeable</li>
  <li>unwavering</li>
</ul>

<h1 id="example">Example</h1>

<p>In spite of <strong>the fact that</strong> increasing weight is very hard, I will be unwavering until I increase my weight.</p>

<p>In spite of <strong>the fact there</strong> are a lot of words and grammar in English, my determination to learn English is unshakeable.</p>

<p>In spite of the journey <strong>being</strong> challenging, I’m determined to keep moving.</p>

<p>Regardles of <strong>the fact that</strong> the day is rainy, I’ll hang out with my friends.</p>]]></content><author><name>Yawei</name></author><category term="English" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hardest thing I’ve ever had to do… key words and phrases In spite of … Regardless of … Despite …]]></summary></entry></feed>